Finding Aid for the Miriam Matthews photograph collection, 1781-1989 LSC.1889
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Black Photographers., 1947-1970.
  - Harry H. Adams., 1960-1970.
    - Business, Professions, Labor (1 of 3). (Box 38, Folder 5)
      Include photographs of Jimmy Hoffa (white), Gladys Root (white). Majority are photographs of black- owned businesses and African American workers.
    - Business, Professions, Labor (2 of 3). (Box 38, Folder 6)
      Includes photographs of black-owned businesses and African American workers. Many unidentified photographs categorized by Miriam Matthews as "Business, Professions, Labor."
    - Business, Professions, Labor (3 of 3). (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - James Baldwin, writer. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Artists and Art Associations. (Box 39, Folder 3)
      Includes photographs of paintings, artists, sculptures.
    - Entertainers (1 of 4). (Box 39, Folder 4)
      Includes photographs of actors, disc jockeys, singers, and other entertainers.
    - Entertainers (2 of 4). (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Entertainers (3 of 4). (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Entertainers (4 of 4). (Box 40, Folder 1)
      Includes photographs of Louis Armstrong, Sammy Davis Jr., Ray Charles, Ella Fitzgerald, Miriam Makeeba, Mahalia Jackson, and other entertainers.
    - Education (1 of 2). (Box 40, Folder 2)
      Includes photographs of schools, playgrounds, students, and educators.
    - Education (2 of 2). (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Social Events, Clubs, Charity (1 of 7). (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Social Events, Clubs, Charity (2 of 7). (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Social Events, Clubs, Charity (3 of 7). (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Social Events, Clubs, Charity (4 of 7). (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Social Events, Clubs, Charity (5 of 7). (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Social Events, Clubs, Charity (6 of 7). (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Social Events, Clubs, Charity (7 of 7). (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - African American families. (Box 41, Folder 5)
      Including Broady family, Davis family, and other unidentified families.
    - Portraits of Children and Infants (1 of 2). (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Portraits of Children and Infants (2 of 2). (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified woman celebrating 100th Birthday. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Los Angeles Sentinel Mother of the Year, five sons in Vietnam., 1967. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Birthday Parties, Stag Parties. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Sports Players (1 of 2). (Box 42, Folder 5)
      Includes baseball, golf, bowling, Little League
    - Sports Players (2 of 2). (Box 42, Folder 6)
      Includes photographs of Joe Louis, Roy Capanella, Archie Moore, Frank Robinson, Jim Brown and other unidentified athletes.
    - Harry H. Adams, Photographer. (Box 42, Folder 7)
      Includes portrait of Adams, photograph of Adams escorting his daughter at a cotillion, a photograph of Adam wearing sunglasses.
  - Ira Sweet., 1947.
    - Central Avenue Scenes., 1947. (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Museum and Gallery Exhibitions., 1980-1987.
  Large mounted photographs, captions, and signage from museum and gallery exhibitions curated or lent by Miriam Matthews.
  - California African American Museum exhibition.
    - Arts and Entertainment (1 of 2). (Box 43)
      Actors, actresses, black motion picture companies, composers, choir directors, soloists, painters, and musicians. Includes Bert Williams, Nat King Cole, Paul Howard, Hattie McDaniel, Dorothy Dandridge, and Alice Taylor Gafford.
    - Arts and Entertainment (2 of 2). (Box 44)
    - Business and Work in early 1900s (1 of 2)., 1900-1910. (Box 45)
      Black-owned businesses and black laborers in Los Angeles. Race newspapers, black mutual aid insurance and loan, the Somerville hotel, trade schools, police officers, and firemen figure prominently.
    - Business and Work in early 1900s (2 of 2)., 1900-1910. (Box 46)
    - Business and work - Western Progress 1928 (1 of 3). (Box 47)
      Articles and images from special issue of Western Progress in 1928 on black businesses in Los Angeles.
    - Business and work - Western Progress 1928 (2 of 3). (Box 48)
    - Business and work - Western Progress 1928 (3 of 3). (Box 49)
    - Business and work - newspapers, mutual aid, Somerville hotel, trade school (1 of 2). (Box 50)
      Other black businesses, especially newspaper agencies, mutual aid, hotel, trade schools.
    - Business and work - newspapers, mutual aid, Somerville hotel, trade school (2 of 2). (Box 51)
    - Churches and Social Organizations (1 of 2). (Box 52)
      Scott United Methodist Church of Pasadena, and First AME Church on Azusa Street. Greek organizations (both social and political), lodges, club women, community organizations, YMCA, YWCA, and NAACP.
    - Churches and Social Organizations (2 of 2). (Box 53)
    - Founders, Explorers, Early Settlers, Early Years (1 of 2). (Box 54)
      Titles given from Miriam Matthews' categorization. "Founders" refers to group of mixed race pobladores who established El Pueblo de Los Angeles for Spain in 1781. Explorers include Jacob Dodson, Peter Ranne, and James Beckwourth. "Early Settlers" refers to those who settled in Southern California between 1781 and 1848, when Spain and then Mexico still controlled the region. The "Early Years" is the period following until the railroad arrived when the population of Los Angeles remained small. Biddy Mason and Robert Owens appear in this final group.
    - Founders, Explorers, Early Settlers, Early Years (2 of 2). (Box 55)
    - Civil Rights, Government Officials, and Civil Rights (1 of 2). (Box 56)
      Civil rights demonstrations, voting, residential restrictions, attorneys, judges, government officials, and politicians.
    - Civil Rights, Government Officials, and Civil Rights (2 of 2). (Box 57)
    - Pioneers (1 of 2)., 1885-1915. (Box 58)
      Mostly middle class African American men and women between 1885 and 1915 in Los Angeles. Organized alphabetically. Included are Benjamin Talbot, John and Margaret Scott, and Ralph Bunche's family the Johnsons, among others.
    - Pioneers (2 of 2). (Box 59)
    - Street Scenes, Parades, Education, Sports (1 of 3). (Box 60)
      Parades such as the Fiesta Parade and Rose Parade. Men and women with their cars. Street scenes of Central Avenue. Sports including aviation horse racing, football, baseball, boxing, and dude ranch. Education including high school students, elementary school and first black principal in Los Angeles, Bessie Bruington Burke.
    - Street Scenes, Parades, Education, Sports (2 of 3). (Box 61)
    - Street Scenes, Parades, Education, Sports (3 of 3). (Box 62)
    - Military. (Box 63)
      Men in military uniform including Titus Alexander, as well as women in the Red Cross.
    - Large Mounted Prints for CAAM exhibit (18x21) (1 of 8). (Box 73)
      Includes enlargements of photographs found elsewhere in this collection relating to sports, business, organizations, Los Angeles founders, churches, entertainment, Greek organizations, early settlers, parades, art, military, police, and fire department in the black community.
    - Large Mounted Prints for CAAM exhibit (18x21) (2 of 8). (Box 74)
    - Large Mounted Prints for CAAM exhibit (18x21) (3 of 8). (Box 75)
    - Large Mounted Prints for CAAM exhibit (18x21) (4 of 8). (Box 76)
    - Large Mounted Prints for CAAM exhibit (18x21) (5 of 8). (Box 77)
    - Large Mounted Prints for CAAM exhibit (18x21) (6 of 8). (Box 78)
    - Large Mounted Prints for CAAM exhibit (18x21) (7 of 8). (Box 79)
    - Large Mounted Prints for CAAM exhibit (18x21) (8 of 8). (Box 80)
    - Large Mounted Prints for CAAM exhibit (21x24) (1 of 2). (Box 81)
    - Large Mounted Prints for CAAM exhibit (21x24) (2 of 2). (Box 82)
  - El Pueblo Historic Monument exhibition., 1987.
    "A Tribute to Afro-American Pioneers"
    - Photographs mounted on goldenrod posterboard. (Box 83)
      Includes photographs of Norman O. Houston, the YMCA Citizen band, the Shackleford family, William Nickerson, M. Earl Grant, Peter Johnson, the first public school in Los Angeles, and other images of daily life in California.
    - Photographs mounted on green posterboard. (Box 84)
      Includes photographs of Robert and Winnie Owens' home, Owens' livery stables, the NAACP, the 104th birthday of Margaret Scott, Second Baptist Church, Robert Curry Owens, Ellen Mason Owens, Biddy Mason
    - Mounted photographs on a mix of green, goldenrod, and rust posterboard (1 of 2). (Box 85)
      Includes photographs of Los Angeles Police and Fire, Mason-Owens families, settlers, professions, murals from Golden State Mutual Life, leading citizens, early business, churches, and organizations.
    - Mounted photographs on a mix of green, goldenrod, and rust posterboard (2 of 2). (Box 86)
    - Mounted photographs on a mix of goldenrod and rust posterboard. (Box 87)
      Includes photographs of the Somerville family, Allensworth, the Roberts family, early black professionals, the Holmes Ave. School, Gen. Andres Pico, the Pico house, Pio Pico and wife, William Grant Still.
    - Mounted photographs on a mix of green and rust posterboard (1 of 2). (Box 88)
      Includes photographs of Titus Alexander, Bessie Burke, Pio Pico, Mr. and Mrs. Dunbar, Hon. James Alexander, E.L. Chew, the Harvey family, Paul R. Williams, and A.C. Garrott.
    - Mounted photographs on a mix of green and rust posterboard (2 of 2). (Box 89)
    - Photographs mounted on green posterboard. (Box 90)
      Includes photographs of police officers, First A.M. E. Church, Scott's Hall, Tom Bradley, Frederick Roberts, and Jesse L. Terry with Los Angeles Housing Authority.
    - Photographs mounted on goldenrod posterboard. (Box 91)
      Includes photographs of Catarina Moreno, Founders monument at the Plaza, Jacob Dodson, Jose Moreno and wife (drawing), Luis Quintero and wife (drawing), Juan Chevez, James Beckwourth, Manuel Camero, map showing ranchos 1784-1810, Maria Rita Valdez adobe, family of Ysidro Reyes, and Manuel Moreno.
  - California Museum of Science and Industry., 1984.
    Exhibit entitled "Blacks in the Building of a Nation and the City of Los Angeles"
    - Mounted photographs and captions (1 of 4). (Box 92)
    - Mounted photographs and captions (2 of 4). (Box 93)
    - Mounted photographs and captions (3 of 4). (Box 94)
    - Mounted photographs and captions (4 of 4). (Box 95)
  - Other Museum and Gallery Exhibitions.
    - Museum Captions and Random Sizes. (Box 64)
    - Museum Captions and Random Sizes. (Box 65)
    - Black Los Angeles Photo exhibit by Miriam Matthews[?]. (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Photographs of black business and labor mounted on cardboard. (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Early Los Angeles photographs mounted on cardboard. (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - "Negroes in California" binder. (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Women of Courage Exhibition., 1986. (Box 66, Folder 5)
      Photographs of awards given to Mabel Gray
    - Photographs of an unidentified exhibition. (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Description of Slides on California Negro History from Miriam Matthews. (Box 66, Folder 7)
      Includes printed descriptions of 56 slides on California Negro History.
    - Slides on California Negro History from Miriam Matthews. (Box 66, Folder 8)
      Includes 80 slides depicting African American history in California. In original order of slide carousel, however, descriptions in next box are numbered differently.
    - Photocopied copies of Los Angeles Building photographs, from Los Angeles Public Library. (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Assorted Captions for Exhibits at the California Museum of Science and Industry (1984), Children's Museum (1981), and El Pueblo Historic Park (1987). (Box 67)
    - Assorted original snapshots and framed photographs. (Box 68)
      May have been part of a museum collection. Includes snapshots of Somerville family, the Sojourner Truth home, an early Los Angeles street scene, a baseball team, a women's club, a large portrait of Betty Hill, prints of pages from John Fowler's "Spreading Joy", a large photograph of the First AME Church (gift to the California African American Museum), print of a painting of W.E.B. Du Bois, Fire Capt. John Powell, a mock wedding at the First A.M.E. Church, a Pasadena church, Knights of Pythias, Junior NAACP, and a party at the Owens' home.
    - Photographs mounted for exhibition, San Francisco Bay Area in early 1900s. (Box 69)
    - Photo albums on early African American history collected by Miriam Matthews, and photographs related to Miriam Matthews life and work. (Box 70)
      Includes DWP Leadership Luncheon, Miriam Matthews honoree, 1983.
    - Clippings on black life., 1980s. (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - South Africa. (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Duplicates of Prominent Individuals.
    - Judge Slater Family. (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Home of Attorney Nash. (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Willis O. Tyler, attorney. (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Duplicate photographs of black professionals. (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Lullaby Guild. (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - "Mrs. John (Margaret) Scott" Binder compiled by Miriam Matthews. (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Thomas A. Greene. (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Originals of Clubs and Organizations.
    - California Federation of Women's Clubs (Pasadena 1916) and Prince Hall Grand Lodge (San Diego 1920). (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Duplicates of Daily Life.
    - Clubs and Organizations. (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Churches, Ministers. (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Politics and Government. (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Police and Fire Departments. (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Military. (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - College Athletes. (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Street Scenes. (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Jimmy Smith. (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Alice Taylor Gafford and family. (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Artists and Musicians. (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Unidentified mural. (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Original photographs 1914-1930.
    - Portrait of Vada Somerville, Hattie McDaniel, and Golden State Mutual Life Insurance. (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Other Individuals and Families.
    - Dockweiler family. (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Weeks family. (Box 71, Folder 14)
      Includes photographs of Fay Weeks Allen
    - Harriet Tubman. (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Wildy family collection. (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Patterson, Coker, Bradley, Pickens, Barr, Morris, Russell, and Frazier families. (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Samuel Danley, certificate of deaconship. (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Higgins. (Box 71, Folder 19)
      Miriam Matthews' godmother.
    - Original photographs of Vivian Marsh, Ralph Bunche, and Angie Harrison Nicholas. (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Framed Original Fire Fighters photographs.
    - Truck no. 30, individual portraits, engines. (Box 96)
  - Posters and Prints.
    - Panorama photographs of early Los Angeles., 1917-1957 (Box 97)
    - Original photographs and prints of clubs, panoramas, etc. (Box 98, Folder 1-7)
- Prominent Individuals and Families., 1885-1980.
  Photographs and negatives of African American families which figure prominently in Miriam Matthews' collection due to their professional success, community service, and/or political activism.
  - Last name "A".
    - African Americans in Los Angeles: Last name "A". (Box 5, Folder 12)
      Includes: Raymond Anderson, Howard Allen, and Aljack Adams
  - Titus Alexander.
    - Titus Alexander, civic leader. (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Portraits of Titus Alexander; group of prominent citizens led by Titus Alexander at Boulder Dam; on a picnic with wife, Charlotta, and Joseph Bass; Titus Alexander in WWI army uniform; Alexander and friends in the California Redwoods; his father James Alexander; bookplate design for the Titus Alexander collection of Negro Life and History
  - Allen Allensworth.
    - Allen Allensworth, portraits. (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Portraits of Allen Allensworth in military uniform; includes passport photograph
    - Homes of Allensworth family in Los Angeles and San Francisco. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Photos relating to town of Allensworth., c. 1908. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Col. Allen Allensworth, military., c. 1900. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Allensworth family., c. 1900. (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Includes portraits of his wife, Josephine Allensworth; daughter, Nella Allensworth (later married Louis Blodgett); daughter Eva Allensworth (later married Harrie Skanks); group photos of daughters with friends.
    - Documents regarding town of Allensworth, anniversary., 1976-1986. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Lucky Baldwin.
    - Lucky Baldwin, property, workers., 1880-1900. (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Private stables at Santa Anita Ranch with black driver; Lucky Baldwin in front of his lagoon; Baldwin's race horse shown with black jockey.
  - Kathryn Barr.
    - Kathryn Barr, first Executive Secretary of Los Angeles Urban League., 1891- 1921. (Box 5, Folder 9)
      (nee: Kathryn Baskins, later Mrs. A. Elmer) Barr organized an employment agency in Los Angeles which later became the Los Angeles Urban League. Individual portrait; photograph with her mother and Roscoe C. Simmons; photograph as young girl with daughters of Dr. A.C Garrott.
  - Louis Blodgett.
    - Louis Blodgett, successful contractor and designer of Golden State Mutual Insurance building. (Box 5, Folder 10)
      Individual portraits and photographs with prominent individuals including Gov. Goodwin Knight. Wife is Nella Allensworth (folder 6)
  - Delilah Beasley.
    - Delilah Beasley, historian and newspaper writer., b. 1871- d.1934. (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Author of Negro Trail-Blazers of California (1919), pioneering work in California black history. Columnist for Oakland Tribune.
  - Charlotta Bass.
    - Charlotta Bass, social life. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Includes photographs of Charlotta Bass with friends and at social club events.
    - Charlotta Bass and the California Eagle newspaper. (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Includes photographs of Charlotta Bass and the California Eagle staff. Bass took over the California Eagle, one of the oldest and longest running activist African American newspapers, as editor in 1912. In 1951, she sold the newspaper to Loren Miller.
    - Charlotta Bass, Congressional candidate., 1950. (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Includes photos from Bass's candidacy for the 14th Congressional district on the Progressive party ticket.
    - Charlotta Bass, Vice Presidential nominee., 1952. (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Includes photographs of Bass as nominee by the Progressive Party for Vice President. She was the first African American woman to run for this office. Her running mate was lawyer Vincent Hallinan.
    - Charlotta Bass, other political activities. (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Includes undated photographs of Bass with other politicians. Also included are photos of Bass's time in the Soviet Union along with W.E.B DuBois.
    - Charlotta Bass, community activism. (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Includes photographs of Bass speaking at Bethel A.M.E. Church in San Francisco in 1965 for Negro History Week; her support and sponsorship of the arts; and her work with activist black preachers.
    - Charlotta Bass, early years and family., undated. (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Includes photographs of Ellis Spears (her father) and Charlotta Spears' class photo
    - Joseph Blackburn Bass, husband of Charlotta, and newspaper editor., undated. (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Includes photographs of Joseph Bass with newspaper staff, wearing garb for the Golden West Lodge of the Benevolent and Paternal Order of Elks with Frederick Roberts, and as a child with his mother.
  - William Beck.
    - Mr. and Mrs. William Beck., undated. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Richard C. O. Benjamin.
    - Richard Charles O'Hara Benjamin, California's first black attorney. (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Portrait with Dr. Monroe A. Majors, California's first black physician. *More photographs of both can be found in Series 2 under subseries "Professions"
  - Mary McLeod Bethune.
    - Mary McLeod Bethune, educator and civil rights leader., b. 1875- d. 1955. (Box 6, Folder 11)
      Bethune lived and worked in Florida, however, this file contains photographs of the Los Angeles black community's celebration of her work. Includes portraits as a young woman, as an older woman, and a negative of an image of a mass meeting at Second Baptist Church honoring Bethune.
  - A.C. Bilbrew.
    - A.C. Bilbrew, community leader, musician, poet, and deputy to Kenneth Hahn (County Supervisor)., 1961, 1963. (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Includes photograph of Bilbrew playing piano (1963) and in a group photograph (1961). Photographed by Harry H. Adams (*See series 3 for more of his work).
  - Bogle family.
    - Bogle family., undated. (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Richard Bogle moved to Oregon Territory in 1851 and married America Waldo 1863. Includes photographs of him and his family.
  - Lorenzo Bowdoin.
    - Lorenzo Bowdoin, NAACP leader., 1950s. (Box 7, Folder 1)
      Includes portraits of Lorenzo, his wife Frances, and family portrait. Also, photographs of Bowdoin being honored by the Women's Study Morning Breakfast Club.
  - Boyd family.
    - Boyd family. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Robert T. Boyd, owner of tonsorial parlor. Wife Emma, children Barrett, Helen, and Willis.
  - Broady family.
    - Broady family., May 1963. (Box 7, Folder 3)
      photograph by Harry H. Adams
  - Mary Jane Broyles.
    - Mary Jane Broyles at her 85th birthday. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Bessie Bruington Burke.
    - Bessie Bruington Burke. (Box 7, Folder 5)
      First African American school teacher in Los Angeles (1911), and first African American principal in Los Angeles (1918). Includes high school graduation portrait (1907), photo of her as a child, as an infant with mother Janie Bruington. *More images of her can be found
  - Ralph Bunche.
    - Ralph Bunche and family. (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Photographs of Ralph Bunche, diplomat and Nobel Peace Prize winner, and his family. *More images of him can be found in series
  - Charles Carr.
    - Charles Carr., c. 1951/1960. (Box 7, Folder 7)
      Portrait of Carr, of Whittier California. USC Digital Collection includes lengthy description of his life on the back of the original photo.
  - Laura Chrisman.
    - Laura Chrisman in front of Chrisman apartments., undated. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Carrie Clemens.
    - Carrie Clemens. (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Portrait of Clemens at age 22 in Sonora. Addressed to sister Jennie.
  - Coates family.
    - Edwin and Helena Harper Coates. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Lorenza Cole.
    - Lorenza Cole at piano (wife of Thomas Cole). (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Cooper/Bright families.
    - Cooper/Bright families. (Box 7, Folder 12)
      Includes photographs of Mr. and Mrs. William H. Cooper, Ezekiel Cooper (son?), Jonas Bright and wife Birdielee (nee: Cooper), and Pearl Cooper (later Mrs. Shadrack Johnson). Pearl Cooper was the first African American to ride in the Pasadena Tournament of Roses in 1903. Also Cornelius Johnson Olympic athlete for the high jump.
  - Floyd C. Covington.
    - Floyd C. Covington as a child., 1918. (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Floyd Covington was a leader of the Los Angeles black community for many decades.
  - Crowe family.
    - Harold Crowe, children of. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Daniel James Cunningham.
    - Daniel James Cunningham., undated. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Danley/Johnson/Saunders families.
    - Edgar Johnson. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Margaret Danley, graduation photo. (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Margaret Danley received M.A. degree from Howard University.
    - Danley family, original small photos. (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Includes Samuel Danley Jr. graduation, McCard family, Theresa B. Harper graduation, Calvin Butler Harper as an infant, Belle Johnson Butler, Marjie Danley.
    - Beverly Johnson and family. (Box 8, Folder 4)
      Includes Beverly, wife Rachel Theresa Saunders, son Harry Johnson and his wife.
    - William and Hester Huston Saunders. (Box 8, Folder 5)